

RAKIBUR RAHMAN

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

An ambitious problem solver who is committed to developing skills with a passion for android applications. Experience in creating logical and innovative solutions to mobile application problems. I think and am precise in everything that I do, and have a keen interest in technology, mobile applications and user experience.

CONTACT

+8801736121557



Natun Bazar, Badda, Dhaka- 1229 rakiburrahman.cse.eng@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/rakibur557



github.com/rakibur557

EDUCATION

Dhaka Internaytional University

BSc. in Computer Science & Engineering

CGPA - 3.92

2020 - Present (3rd year running)

SKILLS

Flutter

Dart, JSON, API, UML, XML, UI, Getx, Provider, Firebase, Animation, SQL(Basic), No-SQL, Git. SEO, Google Analytics.

LANGUAGE

Dart, JAVA, Node JS,

Kotlin (Basic), Python,

C++, and C.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2022

Call Center Executive Techbond IT Limited

2021 - Present

DIU Computer & Programming Club

Treasurer

- · Comes up with unique content for the members.
- Brainstorms innovative ideas for the club's portfolio.
- Works closely with the Research team.

2022 - Present

Hult Prize Organization

Campus Director (2022)

Media and outreach executive (2021)

2021 - Present

DIU CodeChef Chapter Competitive Programming Lead

- Train the members about competitive programming.
- Support and manage problem-solving.
- Question setter to the contests.

CERTIFICATE

Training for Mobile Application and Game Development

Genex Info System Ltd.

Digital Marketing

TechBond IT Ltd

2021 - 2022

BASIS Students Forum DIU Chapter Executive Member

Green School BD

2022 - Present

Chief Executive Officer (CEO)

AWARDS

2022

BDApps National Hackathon - 2022

Team Edgefly - Winner (4th) in Dhaka & Mymenshing Regional Round and finalist.

EXPERTISE

Management Skills Leadership Critical Thinking Team Work **Hosting Events English Language Proficiency** 2021 & 2022

NASA Space Apps Challenge -2021/22

Team Prehim Pro - Global Honorable Mention and winner in Barishal regional round (2022).

Team GreenX - Winner in Comilla regional round (2021).

2021

DIU CPC IT Carnival - 2021

Team Prehim - Winner at DIU CPC IT Carnival - 2021 in Project Showcasing.